I'm so glad you're okay, Kasumi.
If it were me, I'd be by your side more...
Much more than Reo.
Am I so bad?
I…
thought you were my friend!
Don't decide we're friends on your own.
What's going on?
Reo!
Don't come near my girlfriend again.
Let's go.
[Ai-Chan's Secret | Episode 7]
I see.
So, Takumi helped you?
No other guy will see that look on your face.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
- Don't "happen to" let your guard down!
- I didn't!
That kindness of yours is exactly what leads other men on!
I'm sorry, too.
I should have told you he confessed to me.
Takumi found out…
that I'm Mai.
I knew it.
I think he'll keep it quiet.
That's what he told me.
Were you angry?
I might have been jealous of him.
I only see Takumi as a friend.
That's only natural.
All right.
- Shall we turn over a new leaf?
- Pardon?
- Let's go.
- Where?
It's a secret.
What does that mean?
- It's so good! Want some, Reo?
- Sure.
- It is good!
- Yeah!
- Come on! That's too much!
- So yummy.
That's enough. There won't be some left for me!
- Yummy!
- No fair!
Give it back!
- It's cold, huh?
- Yeah.
I'm glad I brought my coat.
Thank you.
♫ You are so free ♫
Should we head home?
No. I don't want to go home yet.
- But it's...
- I mean...
It's finally just the two of us.
Then...
want to come to my place?
My mom works the night shift, so no one's home.
♫ Just wanna, wanna, wanna, wanna go and take it ♫
Wow! You've got good style, Reo!
Oh! This manga is the best!
- Want to borrow it?
- For real?
- Yeah.
- Yay!
But...
Do you understand the implications of coming to a guy's room?
Aiko...
Sex appeal is key. That bra will do nothing for him.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
Why?
Well...
It's just...
I'm sorry.
I got too impatient.
No, it's not that.
I'll just walk you home.
Okay.
This bra is terrible!
Oh? A stalker?
No.
I just walked her home.
So? Did you make my little sis a woman?
That's direct...
Well, I am her brother.
I think I might've rushed things.
I thought I'd feel less nervous if I made her mine quickly.
But Ai is really important to me.
I want to value her feelings more than anything.
Oh, to be young! Youth is the best, huh?
Ritsuki, you reek of booze!
Let me tell you something.
[Kafuu High School]
That's it? Even though you went to his house?
But the "thing" I was wearing was second-rate.
When you go to a guy's place when you're dating
- the guy sort of expects "you-know-what."
- Huh?
So that's how it is.
I don't think you have to rush it,
but as his girlfriend, you have to give it some thought.
Reo's a guy, after all. It's kind of sad.
I see.
That's true, huh?
Let's go pick out some underwear together!
Huh? N-No! It's too much trouble.
- Let's go! Let's go!
- No! No!
- Let's go.
- Why?
- What do you want?
- Nothing!
I heard you helped out Aiko before.
What's this?
I hoped she'd keep it a secret a little bit longer.
Keep your paws off my Aiko.
Big words for someone who can't speak on her behalf.
She called you her friend, didn't she?
Love that begins from friendship isn't so bad.
How nonchalant.
I'm very serious.
So what?
We'll stop there for today!
Tomorrow, I was thinking of having the girls go first.
- Oh? Does Ms. Oyama know?
- Yes, she does.
That's fine, then. Got it.
Don't decide we're friends on your own.
- I'll leave it to you.
- Right. Thank you.
Don't put your guard up so high.
We're friends, right?
Takumi...
I want to be someone you can always depend on.
As friends, of course. Right?
Right.
Stop!
What is this?
- Don't interrupt.
- Huh?
Let the flower of love bloom in others, like it's bloomed for you.
What are you talking about? That's ridiculous.
- Wait!
- Aren't those two surprisingly good together?
Please cooperate so things go well with them!
- Why me?!
- Come on!
Let's go. Come on, let's go.
[Are you coming to Spica today?]
[Sorry, I can't today.]
- Where's Reo?
- I don't know.
But you're together all the time.
Wait! Reo!
He's got a date again?
- Then why don't we go on a date, too? Huh?!
- No way.
I'll take that out.
- Welcome!
- Excuse me.
- Yeah?
Oh? You're...
You're Aiko's...
Here you go.
Boss said you can take a break.
I'm okay.
When I'm working, I don't have to think about anything else.
Why so cryptic?
Oh... Did something happen with Aiko?
No, not really.
For real?! I'm so curious!
What is it?
- It's nothing.
- Right.
Reo's hasn't come yet?
He's not coming today.
What? You don't have a date today?
I wonder where he went.
Maybe he is upset that I left without us doing anything.
I'm sure that's not true.
- Does he hate you now?!
- Where'd you come from?
If thing's aren't working out with you, maybe I could...
Chill out!
If you leave him hanging forever, he's gonna cheat on you—
- He would never!
Gross. We agree on something.
Reo would never do something as dirty as cheating...
Never!
You're so naïve. Reo's a guy, after all.
Men are unfaithful creatures.
You could call it their natural hardwiring, I suppose.
If you look back to the Jomon period and the Stone Age...
they had to in order to further the development of humanity!
Did you bring that up so I could hear it?
[Maid Cafe | Spica]
[Where are you? Call me]
Are you worried about what Ritsuki said?
I don't think Reo's that kind of guy.
I know that!
But...
You are worried, huh?
I knew as soon as I saw you.
- What are you—
- Just one minute.
Just one minute will do.
Not even one minute!
I made it.
Reo!
Not even a minute.
You came.
I'm sorry.
My phone died.
- Heal me.
- Huh?
I wanted to see you.
What's wrong, Reo?
Reo?
[Kafuu High]
Something is off.
Reo, let's play!
Sorry, I have to pass today.
Yes?
He doesn't read my messages, he rushes home.
Something is off.
Definitely.
Even if I asked him where he went, he wouldn't tell me.
But he's up to something. I know it.
How can you say it so confidently?
My wild intuition!
Don't you mean "female intuition"?
Reo?
It's lunch time.
Please wake up.
All right, practice is over for the day. Nice work!
Hey, Reo. What's wrong?
Sorry. I have to rush.
It's totally weird.
He's not talking to me. He went somewhere again today.
- He couldn't concentrate at practice, either.
- Why don't you ask him?
If you're worried, shouldn't you try following him?
Like tailing him?
No, I couldn't do that.
Definitely not.
Yeah, I guess that's wrong.
I guess so.
He went this way, right?
But why did you come, Ikumi?
You two would be lost on your own!
He'll hear us!
[Egawatei]
Huh? But this is...
Thank you for coming!
A part-time job? We were worried for nothing.
He could have told me he had a job!
But why did he hide it?
- Do you think he...?
- Huh?
You're not an idiot, are you, Mai?
Such a great guy is going to waste on you!
What's her deal?
Whoa! Aiko as a girl!
Oh, Ranji! Hey, why is Reo working at your job?
Well... I can't tell you.
Listen to the northern wind or something.
Listen...
I'm just guessing here, but...
your birthday is coming up, right?
So maybe…
Thank you for coming!
I just heard your heart squeezing.
You could hear that?
[Do you have time the day after tomorrow?]
[I do after practice]
[Can I come over to your house?]
For real?
[Yeah]
So? How is it going?
Think you're going to earn enough?
Yeah... One way or another.
Oh, to be young! Youth is the best, right?
Ritsuki, you reek of booze!
Let me tell you something...
Aiko's birthday is coming up soon, right?
Surprisingly, she likes brands like BBRS.
♫ The secret that belongs to only us. 1on1 ♫
You'll be fine!
I'm a tight-lipped guy.
I would never betray a promise between men!
- That is a relief.
- Yeah.
I'm not gonna tell anyone else!
Listen to this! Reo has been working like crazy for Aiko.
What a great guy. Makes you want to cry, huh?
But this is a secret! A secret! You can not tell anyone!
You just told me, though.
You know...
I think I might get a surprise present for my girlfriend, too!
It'd be impossible for you to keep it a surprise.
♫ I don’t seem to be me ♫
All right!
There is no way he wanted us to go shopping because business was slow, right?
Ritsuki wanted to be alone with Hiroko.
It's kind of fun, right? It's almost like a date.
Then, why are you here, Kenji?
What? Come on! Reo and Mai are on a date.
So, you and I can also go on a date...
They are on a date?! Where?
What? Oh… I think they're meeting at the train station.
Ikumi?
I can't do it.
I can't love him without hating them together!
Hey, wait, Ikumi!
Ikumi? Hold on!
♫ I'll steal you away before anyone gets the chance ♫
♫ Lips to exchange ♫
Reo?
Yuka?
[Next time]
Isn't she Reo's first?
I regret breaking up with you.
Was your sincerity a lie?
This person is unexpectedly fragile.
Reo and Yuka were totally lovey-dovey.
Would you like to have a one a one against me?
Beat her to a pulp!
An ex-girlfriend? Unforgivable.
[This drama is a work of fiction]